CURRICULUM VITAE

JOSEPH AMOAKO

Tel: 0249646813/0206632222

Personal information

Date of birth : 10^{TH} AUGUST, 1992.

Place of Birth : Ntotroso

Gender : Male

Marital Status : Married

Nationality : Ghanaian

Language Spoken : English & Twi

E-mail Address : josephamoako850@gmail.com

Driver's License : Category (CE)

PERSONAL PROFILE

As well organizes individual with extensive experience in working within the mine, experience with meeting strict deadline effective communication skills and personal commitment to any assign job. Selfless with an outgoing pernality and determination to accomplish. I am ready and and desire to learn new challenges to help contribute significantly to your organization success, I possess the following;

KEY SKILLS

- Deep concern for safety of others
- Self-motivated
- Very creative
- **Excellent** knowledge of the roads and routes you're **driving** on.
- Confident driving skills.
- ***** Excellent understanding of the highway code and traffic regulations.
- ❖ Patient, responsible, assertive and understanding manner.
- ❖ Ability to work for a long period of time with less or no supervision
- Hardworking and courageous
- Safety and time consciousness
- ❖ Good communication skills.
- ❖ Excellent interpersonal skills

- Can work under less supervision, contain stress, like taking initiatives but under instructions and ready to be challenged in environmental issues.
- ❖ Ability to adjust and adapt to changing situations in a working environment
- Understanding of Newmont Health, Safety, Loss prevention Policies and Process

EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND

Institution YAWUSKROM D/A JUNIOR HIGH SCHOOL

Qualification BECE **Period** 2009

Institution GYAMFI KUMANIN SENIOR HIGH TECHNICAL

Qualification WASSCE

Period 2013

OTHER TRAINING

- ➤ General Site Induction
- ➤ Mine Induction
- > Cyanide Training
- > Safety Conscious
- > Pre-Start Checks
- ➤ Basic Principle In Driving
- ➤ Newmont Driving Permit "MP" Green
- > Safety Representative Newmont-Ahafo

WORKING EXPERIENCE

Company SARFPOK COMPANY LIMITED

Position OFFSIDER
Year Duration 2014-2015

DUTIES

- ❖ Assist in the implementation of projects
- ❖ Perform routine tasks, such as sorting and organizing materials
- Follow established procedures and guidelines
- Operate machinery and equipment under the guidance of the Manager
- ❖ Communicate effectively with team members and management
- Ensure that equipment and tools are maintained and kept in good working condition
- ❖ Provide exceptional customer service to ensure that client needs are met
- ❖ Maintain a clean and safe work environment.

Company MILTRAC
Position OFFSIDER
Year Duration 2015-2016

DUTIES

- **❖** Assist in the implementation of projects
- ❖ Perform routine tasks, such as sorting and organizing materials
- Follow established procedures and guidelines
- ❖ Operate machinery and equipment under the guidance of the Manager
- ❖ Communicate effectively with team members and management
- ❖ Ensure that equipment and tools are maintained and kept in good working condition
- ❖ Provide exceptional customer service to ensure that client needs are met
- * Maintain a clean and safe work environment

Company GPRTU/TUC

Position DRIVER **Year Duration** 2016-2017

DUTIES

- ➤ Pick up and drop off workers at designated locations.
- Follow a planned route according to a time schedule.
- ➤ Help disabled workers get on and off the **bus**.
- ➤ Obey traffic laws, rules and regulations on Newmont Site.
- ➤ Follow procedures to ensure passenger safety

Company PROTEA COIN GROUP GHANA

Position SECURITY/DRIVER/MRU

Year Duration 2017-DATE

DUTIES

- **♣** Save driving habits.
- **♣** Follow all state and Newmont safety regulations and standards on Newmont Site.
- Accurately follow routes, maps, and directions.
- **♣** Open vehicle doors and assist workers.
- **♣** Protect an employer's property and enforce laws.
- ♣ Monitor closed-circuit TV cameras and monitor alarms.
- **♣** Respond to any emergencies.
- **♣** Control visitor and employee building access.
- **♣** Conduct security checks for specified areas.
- **♣** Complete reports on anything they observed while on duty.
- Detain any violators

OTHER LICENSE

NEWMONT PERMIT ("MP") GREEN

REFERENCE

MR. EMMANUEL TETTEH

CONSTRUCTION FOREMAN

SARFPOK COMPANY LIMITED

AHAFO SITE

TEL:0244863089

MR. JOSEPH DE-GRAFT QUANSAH

ASSISTANT MANAGER

PROTEA COIN GROUP GHANA

AHAFO SITE

TEL:02434322617

DANIEL SAGBEDZI

RELINE SUPERVISOR

MILTRAC GHANA LIMITED

TEL:0244749127

MR. EFFAH DOMINIC SUPERINTENDENT MOBILE RESPONSE UNIT

TEL:0548876696